# Named Entity Recognition Dataset - BIO Format
# Project: Named Entity Recognition Dataset
# Author: RSK World
# Website: https://rskworld.in
# Email: help@rskworld.in
# Phone: +91 93305 39277
# Format: Each line contains word and its BIO tag, sentences separated by blank line

Apple B-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
was O
founded O
by O
Steve B-PERSON
Jobs I-PERSON
in O
Cupertino B-LOC
, I-LOC
California I-LOC
on O
April B-DATE
1 I-DATE
, I-DATE
1976 I-DATE
. O

Microsoft B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
is O
headquartered O
in O
Redmond B-LOC
, I-LOC
Washington I-LOC
. O

Elon B-PERSON
Musk I-PERSON
is O
the O
CEO O
of O
Tesla B-ORG
and O
SpaceX B-ORG
. O

The O
conference O
will O
be O
held O
in O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
on O
March B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2024 I-DATE
. O

Amazon B-ORG
Web I-ORG
Services I-ORG
was O
launched O
in O
2006 B-DATE
. O

Google B-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
Menlo B-LOC
Park I-LOC
, I-LOC
California I-LOC
in O
1998 B-DATE
. O

Tim B-PERSON
Cook I-PERSON
became O
CEO O
of O
Apple B-ORG
in O
2011 B-DATE
. O

The O
United B-ORG
Nations I-ORG
is O
located O
in O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
. O

Mark B-PERSON
Zuckerberg I-PERSON
founded O
Facebook B-ORG
in O
2004 B-DATE
. O

NASA B-ORG
launched O
the O
Mars O
rover O
in O
July B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
. O

The O
World B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
is O
based O
in O
Washington B-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C. I-LOC
. O

Satya B-PERSON
Nadella I-PERSON
is O
the O
CEO O
of O
Microsoft B-ORG
. O

Amazon B-ORG
was O
founded O
by O
Jeff B-PERSON
Bezos I-PERSON
in O
Seattle B-LOC
. O

The O
iPhone O
was O
announced O
by O
Apple B-ORG
on O
January B-DATE
9 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2007 I-DATE
. O

Netflix B-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
Los B-LOC
Gatos I-LOC
, I-LOC
California I-LOC
in O
1997 B-DATE
. O

Warren B-PERSON
Buffett I-PERSON
is O
the O
chairman O
of O
Berkshire B-ORG
Hathaway I-ORG
. O

The O
Olympics O
will O
be O
held O
in O
Paris B-LOC
in O
2024 B-DATE
. O

Bill B-PERSON
Gates I-PERSON
co-founded O
Microsoft B-ORG
in O
1975 B-DATE
. O

Twitter B-ORG
was O
acquired O
by O
Elon B-PERSON
Musk I-PERSON
in O
October B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
. O

The O
European B-ORG
Union I-ORG
is O
headquartered O
in O
Brussels B-LOC
. O

Sundar B-PERSON
Pichai I-PERSON
is O
the O
CEO O
of O
Google B-ORG
and O
Alphabet B-ORG
. O

The O
company O
moved O
its O
headquarters O
to O
Austin B-LOC
, I-LOC
Texas I-LOC
in O
2021 B-DATE
. O

Meta B-ORG
Platforms I-ORG
was O
rebranded O
from O
Facebook B-ORG
in O
October B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
. O

Jensen B-PERSON
Huang I-PERSON
is O
the O
founder O
of O
NVIDIA B-ORG
. O

OpenAI B-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
in O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Larry B-PERSON
Page I-PERSON
and O
Sergey B-PERSON
Brin I-PERSON
founded O
Google B-ORG
in O
1998 B-DATE
. O

